# Hadi Gunawan

hadigunawan987@gmail.com | +6285781722743 | South Tangerang, Banten 15224 linkedin.com/in/hadi-gunawan-875889199/

#### **SUMMARY**

Hello, my name is Hadi Gunawan and I am a fresh graduate from University of Pamulang majoring Informatics Engineering (S1), I have work experience for approximately 2 years. I have general knowledge in the IT field from basic to intermediate, I have enthusiasm to have a career in the data field, but do not rule out opportunities in other fields. I like to learn new things and i'm fast learner.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Retention and Winback, Myrepublic ID

Aug 2018 - July 2020

- Make outbound call to costumers who have a disconected status of subscription in order to minimize the occurrence of churn, using customer data from CRM (customer and target oriented)
- Escalated reports related to repairs, terminations and rewards to customers using google sheets, the CRM and tools for instance: Zendesk, internal CRM
- Communicate with other co-worker with same or in another division to achieve target goals

# Data Entry Assistant Intern, BP2T South Tangerang

Jan 2016 - Feb 2016

- Entry data (construction permission) into Microsoft Excel
- Organizing a pysical data into the warehouse and maintaining them

### LICENSE AND CERTIFICATIONS

## SQL Fundamentals Skill Track (DataCamp)

Learning and practicing about Structured Query Language (SQL), in this course I learning about data manipulation, sorting, grouping, filter, aggregate, joins, clauses, subqueries, case, window function, correlated queries, nested queries, Common Table Expressions (CTE), built-in PostgreSQL functions and many more

## Learning Data Analytics (Roadmap by LinkedIn Course)

Learning about data analyst role including soft skills and hard skills such as data cleaning, data manipulation and data visualization using power bi and Ms. excel

Another online course: All About Data (Alterra Academy), RevoU Mini Course Data Analytics (RevoU), Cloud Partitioner Essentials/Learn Basic AWS Cloud (Dicoding Indonesia), Apsara Clouder-Cloud Computing (Alibaba Cloud), Re-Cloud Challanges Indonesia as an participant (Codepolitan)

## **SKILLS**

Hard Skills and Tools: Visual Studio Code, Excel, Word, PowerPoint, SQL, Power Bi, Tableau, Google Sheets, Google Data Studio, HTML, CSS, PHP, Python, Flutter, Adobe Photoshop, Balsamiq Mockups (UI) Soft Skills: Communication, Critical Thinking, Teamwork, Adaptability

### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of** Informatic **Engineering**  **University of Pamulang** 

**Sept 2017 - Aug 2021** 

**GPA: 3.46** 

Relevant coursework: Database, Algorithms and Programming, Data Communication, Statistics, Informatics Logic, Calculus, Basic Physics, Computer Programming, Data Structures, Artificial Intelegence, Decision Support System, Computer Graphics.